Guide to the William A. Reuben Papers TAM.289
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II. Subject Files, 1923-2003.
  - Deutsch, John, undated, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Dies, Martin: Notes re:, undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Divorce: Cynthia Reuben, Jan 4, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Dixler, Elsa: The Nation, FOIA, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - The Documents that Weren't There: Nation Article, Letter to the Editor and Reply from Reuben, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Duggan, Lawrence: Correspondence, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Dugger, Ronnie: The Alliance, Correspondence, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Dun Leavay, Charles A.: Correspondence, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Dun Leavay, Charles A.: "The Rockefellers Ride Again" (excerpts), Aug 1968 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Dun Leavay, Charles A. v. Jester Westy, Inc., Nov 19, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Eddy, George: Correspondence and Memoranda, 1988-1989, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Edgehill Associates, undated, 1978-1998 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Edgehill Associates: "Cultism, Psychology and Politics" (pamphlet), 1989-1999 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Eisler, Gerhart: Notes re:, undated (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Ellsberg, Daniel: Notes re:, undated (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Elsten, David: "Concealed Enemies," Correspondence, re:, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Endore, Guy: Correspondence, Oct 6, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Faulkner, Stanley: Correspondence, Nov 1966 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Feehan, Ramos: Woodstock Typewriter, undated (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Feklisov,: "Klaus Fuks and His Feat", undated (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - The Fiction of Whittaker Chambers: Notes and Typescript, undated (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Finn, Blanche, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Folsom, Franklin, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Foundation Support, undated, 1975, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - FOIA Request: WR, 1976, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Footnote to an Historic Case (Nation Institute), 1983 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Footnote to an Historic Case: Notes, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Footnote to an Historic Case: Owen Opinion, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Footnote to an Historic Case: Owen Opinion, Notes re:, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Footnote to an Historic Case: with Victor Navasky's Comments, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Footnote to an Historic Case: with Zach Sklar's Comments, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Fruchtbaum, Harold: Correspondence re: Alger Hiss, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Fuchs Holzer, Krystal: Interview, Aug 28, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Fuchs, Klaus: Russian Articles re:, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Fuchs Manuscript: Klaus Fuchs and the Atom Spy Conspiracy, Outline, Introduction and Annotation, undated, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Fuchs Manuscript: The Legend of Klaus Fuchs the Atom Spy Who Never Was, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Fund for Investigative Journalism, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Fund for Open Information and Accountability, undated, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Funding for Writing, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Gardner, Virginia: Correspondence, May 11, ???? (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Garlin, Sender: Correspondence, Sep 12, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Gassner, John: Correspondence, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Gettelman, Marvin E.: Correpondence, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Gitlow, Benjamin: Notes, re:, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Godown, Lipton: Woodstock Typewriter, undated, 1962, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Gold, Harry: Notes, Testimony and Analysis, undated, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Gold, Jack: "The Rosenberg Case Revisted", undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Gold, Michael: Interview and Notes, undated, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Goldman, Patti: Coram Nobis and FOIA, undated, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Gornick, Vivian: Correspondence, undated, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Gouzenko Article: Drafts, undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Gouzenko, Igor: Clippings, 1982-1985 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Gouzenko, Igor: Government Documents re:, 1944-1948 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Gouzenko, Igor: Notes re:, undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Gouzenko, Igor: Outline and Research re:, undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - G. P. Putnam and Sons: Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Gray Panthers: Grant Application, Jun 3, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Greenglass, Ruth: FBI Statement, Jul 17, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Gwynn, Beatrice: Correspondence, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Gwynn, Beatrice: Woodstock Typewriter, 1981-1983 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Halper, Albert: Correspondence, Jul 1, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Hamilton, James: Correspondence, 1979-2000 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Hamilton, James: Letter to the Editor, 1983, 1990-1995 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Hamilton, James: Letter to the Editor, 1996-2000 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Hamilton, James: Letter to the Editor, Published, 1990s (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Hamilton, James: Writings, 1977, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Harold Ober Associates: Correspondence, 1975-1996 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Harris, Lement: Correspondence, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Haury, Agnese: Correspondence, undated, 1996-2003 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Helfrich, Carl: Interview and Notes re:, 1949, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Herald, Leon Srabian: Correspondence, 1963, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Harry S. Truman Library Institute, 1978, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Hartshorn, Lewis: "Alger Hiss' Looking-Glass Wars," Notes re:, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Henderson, Loy W.: Interview, Aug 31, ???? (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Herbst, Josephine: Correspondence, Oct 1968-Nov 1968 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Herbst, Josephine: Interview and Notes re:, undated, 1941, 1981, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Hiss, Alger: Government Surveillance, Apr 21, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Hiss, Alger: Grand Jury, undated, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Hiss, Alger and William A. Reuben v. United States Department of Justice, et al.: Addendum, undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Hiss, Alger and William A. Reuben v. United States Department of Justice, et al.: Affidavit in Response to Plaintiff's Rule 6 (e) Motion, Aug 17, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Hiss, Alger and William A. Reuben v. United States Department of Justice, et al.: Affidavit of Eugene F. Yeates, Jul 1, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Hiss, Alger and William A. Reuben v. United States Department of Justice, et al.: Affidavit of Hartford R. Kittel, Oct 17, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Hiss, Alger and William A. Reuben v. United States Department of Justice, et al.: Affidavit of John N. Phillips, Exhibits A and B, undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Hiss, Alger and William A. Reuben v. United States Department of Justice, et al.: Amended Memorandum and Order, Oct 17, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Hiss, Alger and William A. Reuben v. United States Department of Justice, et al.: Answers to Interrogatories on Behalf of the Criminal Division of the Department of Justice, Aug 31, 1977, Sep 23, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Hiss, Alger and William A. Reuben v. United States Department of Justice, et al.: Appendix A, undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Hiss, Alger and William A. Reuben v. United States Department of Justice, et al.: Attorneys, 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Hiss, Alger and William A. Reuben v. United States Department of Justice, et al.: Civil Action Complaint for Declaratory Injunctive and Mandamus Relief, Apr 3, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Hiss, Alger and William A. Reuben v. United States Department of Justice, et al.: Correspondence, re:, 1970s-1980s (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Hiss, Alger and William A. Reuben v. United States Department of Justice, et al.: Declaration of Peter W. Kellen, Oct 28, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Hiss, Alger and William A. Reuben v. United States Department of Justice, et al.: Defendant Fails to Establish that the (b)(3) Exemption was Properly Claimed for Documents 6, 125 and 343, Oct 26, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Hiss, Alger and William A. Reuben v. United States Department of Justice, et al.: Deposition of James Michael Pruitt, undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Hiss, Alger and William A. Reuben v. United States Department of Justice, et al.: Documents Withheld, undated, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Hiss, Alger and William A. Reuben v. United States Department of Justice, et al.: Interrogatories, Jul 6, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Hiss, Alger and William A. Reuben v. United States Department of Justice, et al.: Memorandum in Support of Motion for Summary Judgment, Sep 2, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Hiss, Alger and William A. Reuben v. United States Department of Justice, et al.: Memorandum of Law in Support of a Motion for Summary Judgment on Behalf of Defendants Federal Bureau of Investigation and National Security Agency, Sep 3, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Hiss, Alger and William A. Reuben v. United States Department of Justice, et al.: Motion for Reargument, Oct 28, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Hiss, Alger and William A. Reuben v. United States Department of Justice, et al.: Notice of Motion, Aug 17, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Hiss, Alger and William A. Reuben v. United States Department of Justice, et al.: Notice of Motion, Sep 10, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Hiss, Alger and William A. Reuben v. United States Department of Justice, et al.: Notice of Motion for Summary Judgment, Sep 2, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Hiss, Alger and William A. Reuben v. United States Department of Justice, et al.: Notice of Settlement, Mar 21, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Hiss, Alger and William A. Reuben v. United States Department of Justice, et al.: Plaintiff's Reply Memorandum in Support of a Motion for Summary Judgment, Oct 26, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Hiss, Alger and William A. Reuben v. United States Department of Justice, et al.: Preliminary Statement and Statement of Fact, Sep 3, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Hiss, Alger and William A. Reuben v. United States Department of Justice, et al.: Reply Memorandum in Support of the Motion for Summary Judgment on Behalf of Defendants Federal Bureau of Investigation and National Security Agency and in Opposition to Plaintiff's Motion, Oct 30, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Hiss, Alger and William A. Reuben v. United States Department of Justice, et al.: Stipulation and Order, Jun 7, 1977-Jun 8, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Hiss Case: Baltimore Depositions: Excerpts and Notes, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Hiss Case: Chronology, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Hiss Case: Claude Cross, Attorney, undated, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Hiss Case: Document Examiners, 1948-1949, 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Hiss Case: Ford Automobile, undated, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Hiss Case: Judge Kaufman's Charge, Notes, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Hiss Case: Lawyers, Comments re:, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Hiss Case: Microfilm/"Pumpkin Papers", undated, 1948-1949, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Hiss Case: Second Trial, Bokhara Rug, 1949, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Hiss Case: Thomas Murphy, Testimony and Summation, First Trial, 1950s (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Hiss Case: Woodstock Typewriter, Chain of Possession, 1970s (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Hiss Case: Woodstock Typewriter, Forgeries, undated, 1975, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Hiss Case: Woodstock Typewriter, Investigation, 1950s-1960s (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Hiss Case: Woodstock Typewriter, Notes, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Hiss, Donald: FOIA Request, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Hiss, Donald: Memoranda and Notes, re:, undated, 1949, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Hiss, Isabel Johnson, undated, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Preface, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Introduction, Undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Introduction, Undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Introduction (Stone Hill Publishing), 1980s-1990s (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 1, Director, undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 1, Our Man in Washington, Undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 1, Where it all Began, Sep 11, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 2, Exorcist, Undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 2, Naming Names, Sep 11, 1997, Undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 3, Adolph Berle, undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 3, The Informer, Sep 11, 1997, Undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 4, The Berle Syndrome, Sep 11, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 4, The Gregory File, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 4, Informer, Undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 4, This is Your FBI, Undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 5, The Gouzenko Connection, Sep 11, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 5, Informer, Undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 5, Investigator, Undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 6, Fatal Error, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 6, The Gouzenko Connection, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 6, The Gregory File, Sep 11, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 6, Secret Agents, Undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 7, Gregory File, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 7, Notes, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 7, Theme with Variations, Sep 11, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 7, Where It All Began, Undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 8, Are You or Have You Ever Been?, Undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 8, Clandestine Rendezvous, Undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 8, Secret Agents, 1997, Undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 9, Are You Now or Have You Ever Been, Sep 11, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 9, Spies and Lies, Undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 9, Under Suspicion, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 10, Are You Now or Have You Ever Been?, Undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 10, Behind Closed Doors, undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 10, Our Man in Washington, Undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 10, Under Suspicion, Sep 11, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 11, A Citizen Under Suspicion, Undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 11, Best Friends, Undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 11, Confrontation, undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 11, Let the Public be the Judge, Undated (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 11, Our Man in Washington, Sep 11, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 12, Undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 12, A Citizen under Suspicion, Sep 11, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 12, The Grand Jury Finds, undated (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 12, Under Suspicion, Undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 13, A Citizen Under Suspicion, Undated (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 13, Drafts and Notes, undated (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 13, The Jury Finds, Sep 11, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 13, Libel, undated (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 14, Baltimore Documents, undated (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 14, Going Public, Sep 11, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 14, Grand Jury Finds, Undated (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 15, Fatal Error, Oct 23, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 16, undated (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 16, Clandestine Rendezvous, Sep 23, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 17, Spies and Lies, Sep 23, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 18, Behind Closed Doors, Sep 11, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 18, Confrontation, Undated (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 19, Confrontation, Sep 11, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 20, Let the Public Be the Judge, Sep 23, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 21, Election Returns, Oct 6, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 21, Libel, Undated (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 22, Libel, Sep 11, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 23, Baltimore Documents, Sep 11, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 24, Peter Shepherd's Comments, 1997-1998 (Box 9a, Folder 1)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 24, Pumpkin Papers and Other Capers, Undated (Box 9a, Folder 2)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 24, Under Suspicion, Oct 20, 1997 (Box 9a, Folder 3)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 25, Pumpkin Papers and Other Capers, Aug 8, 1998 (Box 9a, Folder 4)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 26, Now is the Time, 1998-1999 (Box 9a, Folder 5)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 26, Treason, undated (Box 9a, Folder 6)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 27, Now is the Time, Dec 9, 1998 (Box 9a, Folder 7)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 29, The Venue, undated (Box 9a, Folder 8)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 30, The Crucible I, Jan 25, 2000 (Box 9a, Folder 9)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 31, The Crucible II, Jan 20, 2000 (Box 9a, Folder 10)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 32, The Crucible III, Mar 3, 2000 (Box 9a, Folder 11)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Chapter 33, The Crucible IV, undated (Box 9a, Folder 12)
  - Hiss Manuscript: First Trial, undated (Box 9a, Folder 13)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Second Trial, undated (Box 9a, Folder 14)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Second Trial, Chapter 7, undated (Box 9a, Folder 15)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Coram Nobis, Chambers Break with Communist Party, undated (Box 9a, Folder 16)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Coram Nobis, Edith Murray, undated, 1949 (Box 9a, Folder 17)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Coram Nobis, John Lowenthal's Comments, undated (Box 9a, Folder 18)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Coram Nobis, Julian Wadleigh, 1990s (Box 9a, Folder 19)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Coram Nobis, Mary Yates' Comments, undated (Box 9a, Folder 20)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Coram Nobis, Peter Shepherd's Comments, 1982-1983 (Box 9a, Folder 21)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Coram Nobis, Third Draft, undated (Box 9a, Folder 22)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Crimes of Alger Hiss Outline, 2000 (Box 9a, Folder 23)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Elizabeth Bentley, Jul 1997 (Box 9a, Folder 24)
  - Hiss Manuscript: The Frame-Up of Alger Hiss(Stone Hill Publishing), 1976 (Box 9a, Folder 25)
  - Hiss Manuscript: General, Undated (Box 9a, Folder 26)
  - Hiss Manuscript: General, Undated (Box 9a, Folder 27)
  - Hiss Manuscript: General, Undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Hiss Manuscript: General, Undated (Box 10, Folder 1a)
  - Hiss Manuscript: The Hiss Case, A New Look, Draft and Outline, undated (Box 10, Folder 1b)
  - Hiss Manuscript: The Hiss Syndrome, Correspondence re:, 1966-1974, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 1c)
  - Hiss Manuscript: The Hiss Syndrome, Outline, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Hiss Manuscript: The Hiss Syndrome, Publisher's Agreement, Simon and Schuster, Inc., 1968 (Box 10, Folder 2a)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Peter Shepherd's Comments, 1970s-1990s (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Hiss Manuscript: Table of Contents, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Hiss, Tony: Correspondence, 1997-2001 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - The Honorable Mr. Nixon: Publicity, 1956-1960 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - HUAC: Background Data for Hearing, Aug 1948 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - HUAC: Reports and Notes, re:, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Hughes, Langston: Correspondence with Meyer Zeligs re: Chambers (photocopy), Apr 24, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Hunter College: James Aronson Award, 1989-1996, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Hutchins, Grace: Interviews, 1949, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Hutchinson, Stuart: Ram's Horn Productions, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Hyland, Thomas: Interview, Jun 23, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Institute for Media Analysis: Anti-Communism in the United States, Conference, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Josephson, Harold: "Benjamin Gitlow: The Making of an Ex-Communist Witness", 1980 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Josephson, Harold: Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Josephson, Leon: Interview and Notes re:, undated, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Josephson, Matthew: Correspondence, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Jowitt, Earl: Notes re:, undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Karmen, Andrew: "A Preliminary Report on the Finances of the Greenglasses" and "Report on the Greenglasses' Finances", Jul 1, 1978, Jun 1, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Kluger, Richard: Correspondence, Jan 10, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Koecher, Karl F.: Spy Case, 1980s (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Krieger, Sam, undated, 1971-1980 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Krieger, Sam and Jonah Raskin: "A Radical Odyssey: From the Wobblies to the Teamsters", undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Krieger, Sam: Legal Fund to Clear Sam Krieger, undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Krieger, Sam: "Whittaker Chambers: The False Witness Who Sent Hiss to Prison and Elected Nixon President", undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Krivitsky, Walter: Correspondence and Notes re:, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Kroger, Helen and Peter, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Kuchment, Mark: "The Rosenberg Case and the Sarant-Barr Story", undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Lader, Lawrence: Corporation Crime, Book Outline, undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Lader, Lawrence: Power on the Left, re:, undated, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - LaFlour, Mark: Correspondence, Jun 22, 1905 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Lamont, Corliss, undated, 1976, 1992, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Lamphere, Robert, 1976-1977, 1982, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Lane, Chester T.: Correspondence, undated, 1953, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Lapham, Lewis H.: Correspondence, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Lasky, Victor: Correspondence, undated (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Lehrman, Nathaniel S.: Correspondence, 1980-1981, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Lehrman, Nathaniel S. and Aaron Katz: "Judge Irving R. Kaufman--A Time to Speak", undated (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Letters to the Editor, 1974, 1984, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Letters to the Editor: Commentary, 1988, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Letters to the Editor: Hiss Obituaries, re:, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Letters to the Editor: Nixon, re:, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Letters to the Editor: Policy Review, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Letters to the Editor: Returned, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Letters to the Editor: Washington Post, undated, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Levin, David: Perjury, Correspondence and Review re:, 19-Oct, -78 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Levine, Nathan: Government Documents and Notes,re:, undated, 1969, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Levinson, Mike: Correspondence, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Levitt, Morton: "Richard Nixon and Alger Hiss: A Psycho Historical Reprise", undated (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Lieber, Maxim: Correspondence, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Liebling, A. J.: Correspondence, May 16, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Lockey, Ira: Notes re:, undated (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Lowenfish, Lee: "Joseph Freeman: The Private Disillusionment of a Lyric Radical", 1980 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Lumpkin, Grace: Correspondence, Jan 2, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Machlis, Joseph: Clippings and Correspondence, 1971, 1991, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Macleod, Norman: Correspondence, Apr 11, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Marbury, William L.: "The Hiss Case", Jun 1977 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Massing, Hede: Testimony and Notes re:, undated, 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - May, Gary: Correspondence, Dec 24, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - McCarren Act, undated, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - McCloskey, Jeannie R.: Correspondence, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - McLean, Edward: Correspondence, 1950s-1960s (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Meeropol, Michael and Robert: Venona Documents re: Rosenbergs, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 1)